Quick break
All I know what I'm supposed to do?
Fight for the
Fight for the way.
Take-off the door, and take-off the door.
Let's start with
the new world.
Look at it! I've been waiting for a
few years to
take a look.
I'm not going to hold it to my own desire.
I believe that I'm not going
to be one of my own dreams.
I believe
that I'm going
to be one of my own dreams.
Keep running, Luffy! Don't stop!
It can't be.
Do something!
It's all over, isn't it?
It's too late to put
out the fire, Captain.
We gotta abandon the ship.
The sea is blocked off anyway.
Damn it, Kate.
That filthy cheat thinks
he can get away with this?
Just you wait! You're dead!
Must Grey Terminal be an assault to
my senses even in its final moments?
That light is far too bright.
We are sorry, Your Majesty.
Please, allow us to close the curtains.
Say, Papa, how come we want to
burn everybody in Great Terminal?
Aren't they people, too, just like us?
Not exactly.
They chose to live meaningless lives.
Just think about it.
If they had chosen the path of
high-class nobility like you and me,
they wouldn't be in this mess.
They wouldn't?
I get it!
You mean it's their fault for
being born all poor and dumb!
How silly!
Yes, now enough about those people.
You need to get some
studying done before bedtime.
Okay!
See you tomorrow.
Hmm.
It's blocked off here
too damn it we just keep
losing ground I don't
want to die like this
Do you think all those old guys got away
safe who cares about them we're in trouble
Crap I can't tell where are we who said
you two brats were allowed to escape
Blue Jam!
How come you're still here?
I thought you were escaping
after the fire got lit.
Did something happen?
Shut up, you punk!
It's hopeless.
You do know that, right?
There's a sort of irony to this.
It's a new perspective.
Humans are strange creatures.
I hit rock bottom, and all
I can do is laugh about it.
They're acting really weird.
It's creepy.
Luffy, run for it! Run him!
Where do you think you're going?
We did this job together.
That means we get to die together.
We're not going to die with you losers.
We don't give up that easy.
Is that so?
Actually, you still haven't told me
where you're hiding that treasure.
Friends don't keep
secrets from each other.
I'll save it for you
before the fire reaches it.
All you have to do is tell me where it is.
Your life is in danger, and
all you care about is treasure?
Well, if you don't want it, then
you might as well tell me, right?
Damn it.
You got nuts.
I'm just trying to stop another tragedy.
I already saw my ship reduced to charcoal.
It'd be a shame if that
happened to your treasure, too.
All your hard work and for nothing.
You suck!
Get your own treasure!
All right, you win.
No!
You spent forever collecting that!
What would Sabo think? Shut up!
Sabo would understand.
The treasure isn't important anymore.
The only thing that matters
is getting out of here alive.
Hey
Six years we've collected treasure
for six years and hit it in this tree.
Why thank you
Don't cry it's okay Luffy
this won't be the end
What are you doing?
I told you where it is, now let us go!
I'm sorry.
I don't think I trust you.
Now then, about that treasure.
Let's go. You can lead. You moron!
That won't leave us time to
escape, and I'm not dying here!
Just go!
You've got the damn map!
Listen, kid.
Don't you dare piss me off.
I'm not above stealing from
children or murdering them.
I'll have my revenge and believe
me those nobles will regret
the day they cross blue jam and
to think you called one of them!
Your brother they act
like a little money and
influence makes them a gift
to the rest of the world!
Like it gives them the right to
look down on us like we're trash!
Shut up Sabo isn't like
that. Take it back. Yes.
He is face it
Sure, you stayed together, but he was
looking down on you the whole time
Liar!
His parents are loaded.
He doesn't have any of the
problems that you or I deal with.
He used you idiots to get some kicks.
He was just bored, then
got a taste of real life,
and he ran back home to his rich daddy!
That's enough!
Sabo is our brother! He's right!
Sabo just wants to be free!
Lucy!
Say goodbye, kid.
Just let me go!
Get the hell away from Luffy!
Hey, talk to me!
What the hell did you do?
You screwed a big time, brat!
Go on!
Try that crap again before I kill you!
Get off of me, you scumbag!
Time's up.
Please, no!
Don't do it!
Denon!
Don't you dare hurt my boys.
I'm not afraid to kill you!
Thanks, but what are you guys doing here?
We aren't too late, are we?
Yikes, you got roughed up
pretty bad, Luffy. You okay?
I'll make it.
And what about Sabo?
I don't see him.
He's safe in Hightown.
He isn't with us anymore.
Easy now.
I know you.
You're that bandit
gorilla from Mount Grove.
Bandit, yes.
Gorilla, no.
But that's not the point here.
The point is, like it or not,
these kids are my responsibility.
Let's dance.
Now!
Everybody run!
Hurry up!
What are you doing?
Ace, we gotta get going.
What's the matter?
I'm staying.
I won't run.
You've got nothing to gain
here, you little idiot!
Look, this place is on fire!
Also, Blue Jam is a hardened criminal.
A little kid like you shouldn't
be fighting him to the death!
I...
I gotta help him!
Cut it out! Damn it! Stop!
Take Luffy, and get your
butts back to the hideout.
What about you?
I'll take care of Ace, no matter
how many asses I gotta kick.
You're so cool!
Now come!
Yes, ma 'am!
Come home safe, boss!
We'll be waiting for you!
Look at that. How brave.
But at the end of the day, you're just
a woman and a child against a pirate.
Do you like those odds?
Only two kinds of people
survive in battle.
The strong and the cowardly.
Bravery doesn't enter
the picture, I'm afraid.
Oh, is that so?
Hmm, have it your way.
Take that off!
We're all dead!
Look around you!
There's no way out now!
Everything was fine!
How could this happen so quickly?
I'm burning!
You and everyone else!
Just let me die already!
What the heck was that?
Hey, it made a path through the fire.
Whoa, did somebody do that on purpose?
Who cares?
Now we can get out of this hellhole.
Hey, look, you guys.
There's a ship here.
It's waiting down by the shore.
I don't know who and I don't know how,
but I think they're here to save us.
Let's go.
Hurry, before the fire comes back.
I've seen nobles do some dreadful things,
but this takes the cake
absolutely reprehensible!
Anywho, this locale is rather out of
the way how did you hear the news?
Were you keeping an eye on this country or
perhaps is there something
here of interest to you?
What's happening here will happen
in the rest of the world soon enough
human beings can't be thrown away!
A world that allows that must change!
No matter how long it takes, I will
stop out this misery and injustice!
I can't stay here because if
I do then I'll never be free!
The children born in this country must
have a future that they can believe in.
If it's freedom you want, so long as
you have the will to fight for it,
you are welcome aboard this ship!
Are you sure that wall will protect us?
It seems like the fire could
spread here any second.
It won't last long.
Surely they'll lead us into
Hightown until it passes.
Not a chance.
Those gates are so tight,
even a flea can't get through.
Let me go!
Come back, boss!
Ace, too!
No, you can't die!
No matter how their friends cried,
Ace and Dadan did not emerge from
the flames consuming Gray Terminal.
Easy, kiddo.
You're still hurt.
What are you doing?
What do you think?
I'm looking for Ace and Dadan.
That's not gonna work.
I'm worried, too.
But for right now, we just have to wait.
The military is down in Great Terminal.
Word is they were sent in to clean up
everything after the fire died down.
And by clean up, I mean take
care of any remaining evidence.
I'm sure that extends to
killing off the survivors, too.
You'll be no exception.
But, Ace!
I can't just leave him out there!
And we have to let Zappo
know that we didn't die!
Orders say to shoot any
survivors we find on sight.
Yeah, what survivors? It's weird, though.
I've hardly seen any corpses.
That fire was pretty intense.
Probably burned up their bones, too.
I was up all night, scared that
fire would get over the wall.
Should have known they wouldn't
burn decent people like us.
I heard Blue Jam's ship
wasn't quite so lucky.
Good.
Let's hope the bastard
was on it when it burned.
Can't you see it will
always end this way, Sabo?
The police and military
have photos of you.
Try all you want.
There's no escape.
You'll never get out of Hightown,
let alone this house, unless
I expressly permit it.
I need you on guard duty.
Now, I'll look into
getting you new uniforms.
I'm sorry, sir, but we have other duties.
I'm a nobleman.
That means I get what I want.
Don't worry, I'll have a
word with your superiors.
Yes, sir.
Listen, Sabo, it's not too late for you.
From now on, you'll lock yourself in
your room and learn to be a proper noble.
No!
I don't want to be cruel,
but I am certainly capable of it
and anything else I so desire.
You could disappear,
just like your friends.
Are we clear?
I think so.
Ace. Luffy.
If Stella can study hard, then so can you.
Everything will work out fine.
And then your parents,
who work so hard to build a proper
future for you, can finally be happy.
Won't that be nice?
I'm sure it'll be nice for you as well.
Just give it some time.
Papa!
If you're sad, I can help.
Dependable as always, Stella.
We've got that big ceremony
coming up, you know.
Let's buy you some new clothes.
You'll look so handsome
for the Celestial Dragon.
Study hard, and I'll check
your homework tomorrow.
Have a pleasant afternoon.
Don't worry, guys.
I'm fine.
And you're tough.
So I know you're okay, too.
There's no way you died in that fire.
I just wish I could see you, even once.
But if people follow me,
they'll find out you're still alive
and you'll be in danger again.
It looks nice from the outside,
but this house is a birdcage.
I'm going to lose my mind if I have to
stay in this stuffy, stuck-up place.
I thought I found freedom, but
it seems to keep slipping away.
All right, we're off.
Take good care of Sabo.
We won't be back until
late. Yes, sir. As you wish.
After much anticipation,
the day of the World Nobles' visit
to the Goa Kingdom arrives at last.
A lavish ceremony is prepared to greet
his ship as it enters the harbor.
Hey, wait!
Is that a ship leaving port?
A what? What?
A fishing boat?
Hey!
Come back!
You're blocking their path!
Why, it's just a child.
A little boy is steering that boat.
Then he's a noble?
But surely all the
families are here watching.
It can't be.
Nice weather today.
It's just perfect for setting sail.
Uh, crap! That's mine! It was stolen!
I have nothing to do with this mess!
His flag!
He's got a Jolly Roger on it.
Is he trying to be a pirate or something?
Does it matter?
The kid's flag isn't the issue here.
He's heading straight for the ship.
The Celestial Dragon
isn't gonna like this.
Either you lose that boat
or you lose your job!
Do you hear me?
Fix it now!
Uh, yes, sir.
Hey!
Get back here, kid! Are you nuts?
I'm not afraid of anything
as long as I'm free.
I just have to be far away from here.
I have to follow my own dream.
Nobody's gonna change me.
Huh?
Holy crap, Sabo.
What do you think you're doing out there?
Give them a warm welcome, everyone!
Wow, that's one big ship.
It could run right over me easy.
Let's avoid that, shall we?
This is a first for me!
The Celestial Dragons hardly
ever make visits like this!
I hope nobody mucks this up!
We didn't burn all those
people for nothing!
What is that wretched little thing?
It seems to be a fishing boat, sir.
That's so cool!
I hope I'm the captain of a
big ship like that some day.
Get out of my way!
I gotta find eggs!
Easy, Luffy, easy.
I know how you feel, but
it's still too dangerous.
You got banged up pretty bad and
the place is crawling with soldiers.
Who cares?
Please come down and listen to me.
We get it.
We're scared too.
But right now, we just need to have faith
that the boss and ace are still alive.
Tiger went back to look
for him, so be patient.
Understand?
This is hard on everyone, OK?
The fishing boat has been hit.
What happened to the child?
That kid shouldn't have gotten
in the Celestial Dragon's way!
Get out of there!
Damn!
Why'd he shoot at me?
St.
Jalmec, there's a child on that ship!
Anyone who flies a black
flag is a filthy pirate.
His age is irrelevant.
He must pay.
Come on!
A commoner should know better.
Don't cross my ship,
you stupid pirate brat!
What?
Why would they fire on
that ship a second time?
Who cares?
We don't want to make
the celestial dragon mad.
This is an important ceremony.
Let him do whatever he wants.
Clear the wreckage already!
Hey, I got news.
Ace and the boss are...
What is it?
They came back.
They both made it.
I was...
so scared.
She's badly wounded.
Get them both inside.
Now!
Hurry!
Hang in there, boss.
Ace!
Get off!
Come on.
Did you seriously think I was dead?
Baby!
Quit crying already!
I'm standing right in front of you, dummy!
Come on, Ace.
Take it easy on the kiddo for once.
Luffy's just happy to see you.
What happened the night of the fire?
We all came back here with Luffy,
so we haven't heard a word.
Can you tell us everything that
happened to you and the boss?
Oh.
Well, um, we fought Blue Jam.
We barely defeated him.
And we tried to catch up to
you guys as fast as we could.
But the fire was blocking our way.
We made it through the fire.
Dadan was suffering from
some serious burns, though.
Eventually, we managed to get to the
riverside in the In-Between Forest.
I went into town to steal medicine
and grab whatever food I could find.
I'm no doctor, but I did what
I could to save Dedan's life.
What an ordeal!
In any case, all that matters is that
both of you are back safe. I'm sorry.
I made you worry.
That fire was huge, and they
were hunting down survivors.
Sabo must think we're dead right now.
This kingdom's likely full of lowly
plebeians that will get in my way.
Be on the lookout for any disruption.
Right.
I wonder what Sava's been up to.
But at least Ace finally
made it back, right?
He even carried Dadan home with them.
Ace, when I came for you...
I'm staying!
I won't run.
Why did you do that?
I don't know.
I can't help but get fired up.
I'm afraid if I run, that I might
leave something important behind me.
So I fight.
Luffy was there, so I had no choice.
It's tough to explain,
but I think that's why.
Even when he faced a wave of
far more powerful enemies,
Roger would never think of running away.
Did that fool have a death wish?
Running away is a strategy too.
For him, it wasn't even
an option. Think about it.
Retreat means leaving people behind.
If Roger ran, he'd be abandoning
his crew, the people he loved most.
So when you think about it,
it's not that he wouldn't run.
Rather, he made sure the enemy
couldn't go after his crew.
He always protected them.
He was a different kind of
animal in times like those.
He once wrecked a whole
country's army because
some soldiers decided to
mouth off about his men.
When he was angry,
Roger would get violent.
He was selfish and short-tempered,
but he wore his heart on his sleeve.
He was like a boy that never grew up.
For better or worse, his
childhood was a lot like Aces.
The pain he went through just made him
hold on tighter to the ones he loved.
Roger could be a very reckless man, but
he lived to become king of the pirates.
No easy feat.
Despite his flaws and his bad reputation,
his crew still trusted him completely.
Sure, I may be a marine, but
even I can't help respecting him!
That's why I decided to take care of Ace.
I'm the one taking care of him, you ass!
Do you got something
you want to say to me?
No, never mind.
People all over the
world still hate Roger!
And even though Ace holds
a grudge against him too?
They really are like father, like son.
All right, wonder who's gonna win?
Dogra!
You went to town to look
for Asa to dawn, right?
Surprise, they came back home already!
Did they really?
That's just great. Perfect.
What? Sabo?
That can't be.
You're lying to me, dammit!
Why would you even joke
about that kind of thing?
Take it easy!
I told you exactly what I saw, I swear.
I know how you feel.
Everything happened so fast,
I could hardly believe it.
It felt like a nightmare, but
I know that was Sabo. Shut up.
We watched him go back with his
dad to their home in Hightown.
You can't have seen him
out at sea by himself.
That's right.
Sabo is with his family.
And it's like us know how he feels.
We know what it means to be turned
away from your home, to be free.
Sabo didn't want to be a noble.
If he was truly happy, he
wouldn't have gone out to sea.
And the Sabo I saw wasn't just
sailing away from his family.
He was flying a Jolly Roger.
We shouldn't have let him go.
It's all our fault.
Even if I had parents, I was still alone.
Sabo, why didn't we go back into
town and bring him back here?
We're so stupid.
Tell me where I can find
the bastard that killed him.
I'm going to beat him to
death with my bare hands.
You can't kill a celestial dragon.
That's impossible.
I'll make him pay.
Hold on, Ace.
Enough of that, you little punk.
You think you're so tough when you're
really just a cocky, stubborn little brat.
What can you do against a world noble?
You think he's just some thug?
You're just some no-name kid.
You'll die and nobody will give a crap.
Swept under the rug the very next day.
It was this whole rotten
country that killed Sabo.
This rotten world.
What can a scrawny brat
like you do about it?
Your father, on the other hand,
changed the world with his death.
When you become a man as important as him,
then and only then can you take revenge.
Tie this fool up.
Yes, ma 'am.
Zappa!
Dammit!
Shut up, Luffy!
Quit crying like a girl
or else I'll... Ow!
You've come to your senses now, I hope.
Guys, untie him. Right.
Try to keep your cool, okay?
Where's Luffy?
He was crying all night.
Finally fell asleep.
Oh my gosh!
You're not gonna believe this!
We got a letter!
It's from Sabo!
He must have sent it before he left!
Look, I think it's really from him!
Give it!
Don't worry, I won't head to town.
It's for Luffy and me, isn't it?
Ace! Luffy!
I hope you guys weren't hurt in the fire.
I'm worried about you both, but
something tells me you're okay.
I've got a surprise to tell you.
By the time you get this
letter, I'll be long gone.
That's right, I'm heading out to sea.
One thing led to another, and I
decided to set out before you two.
I don't know where I'm going yet,
but I do know that anywhere
will be better than this place.
And don't worry, I haven't
given up on my dream.
I'm still gonna be a pirate.
I got a head start, but I'm
sure you'll catch up in no time.
When we meet again, we'll be unstoppable.
We'll have our reunion on the Grand Line.
Three pirate captains,
more free than the wind.
By the way, Ace, I'm curious.
Which one of us do you think
is the real big brother?
Anyway, wherever we sail, we'll
always have our brotherhood.
It may sound kinda cheesy, but that bond
is what I treasure most in this world.
Luffy is still weak, and a crybaby.
Who knows if he'll ever grow out of that.
But he's still our little brother,
so please take good care of him.
G-g-g-g-g